Can you change your past without destroying your future?
The Butterfly Effect 2 is a drama, science fiction,
thriller film directed by John R. Leonetti.
After his girlfriend, Julie, and two best friends are killed in a tragic
auto accident, Nick struggles to cope with his loss and grief.
Suffering from migraine-like seizures, Nick soon discovers that he
has the power to change the past via his memories.
However, his time-traveling attempts to alter the past and save his
one true love have unexpected and dire consequences.
Nick Larson, played by Eric Lively.
Julie Miller, played by Erica Durance.
Trevor Eastman, played by Dustin Milligan.
Amanda, played by Gina Holden.
Katherine Larson, played by Susan Hogan.
Dave Bristol, played by David James Lewis.
The Butterfly Effect 2 is a 2006 American science fiction
psychological thriller film directed by John R.
Leonetti and starring Eric Lively, Erica Durance,
Dustin Milligan and Gina Holden.
The film is largely unrelated to the 2004 film The Butterfly Effect
and was released direct-to-video on October 10, 2006.
It is followed by The Butterfly Effect 3: Revelations (2009).
The film grossed $966,458 in box office and $2.9 million in home video sales.
The film received generally negative reviews, with reviewers criticizing its
formulaic copy of the first film, simply with different characters.
The film explores themes of suicide, brain tumor, underwear, time travel.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.